<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog &#8211; TriniSwap</title>
	<atom:link href="/wordpress/category/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/wordpress</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency for the people, by the people</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 16:11:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/cropped-triniswap-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Blog &#8211; TriniSwap</title>
	<link>/wordpress</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>TriniSwap : Official Launch</title>
		<link>/wordpress/2020/12/22/triniswap-official-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[triniswap]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 01:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wordpress/?p=296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Introducing Trinidad &#38; Tobago’s first open source decentralized finance project called TriniSwap (TRINI). The goal of TriniSwap is to bring adoption and seamless access to cryptocurrency trading and investing for]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Introducing Trinidad &amp; Tobago’s first open source decentralized finance project called TriniSwap (TRINI). The goal of TriniSwap is to bring adoption and seamless access to cryptocurrency trading and investing for the average person by developing decentralized apps and smart contracts. If you are new to cryptocurrency, to get started visit.&nbsp;<a href="http://docs.triniswap.com/">http://docs.triniswap.com/</a></p>



<p>Say goodbye to inflated crypto prices, high transaction fees and centralized companies that do not give you ownership of your accounts private keys. TriniSwap will enable users to trade cryptocurrencies while being in control of their own funds, our token will give users ownership of the the liquidity pool. Liquidity Providers get 0.3% of every transaction. TRINI token also allows users to partake in the governance of the project. Our main goal is to build a sustainable ecosystem that is fast and reliable for immutable transactions and payments at anytime, anywhere, for everyone.&nbsp;</p>



<p>TriniSwap currently consists of a decentralized exchange and token bridge presently. For our exchange instead of launching our own Solidity Contract, we decided to use an already existing smart contract called Honeyswap (forked from Uniswap Protocol). Our reasoning for going this direction is to prevent potential bugs and liquidity attacks in the genesis stage of building a community, ensuring that our users funds are always secured from malicious actors. We chose to migrate from Ethereum Mainnet to DAI Network Side chain. By doing so, we drastically increase transaction speeds, and reduces the transaction costs to less than $.001 USD. This will enable us to perform micro transactions, scaling the token’s usability. Due to high gas fees, our vision will not be possible at this current time on Ethereum Mainnet, if all goes well with Eth 2.0, we would be happy to bridge the tokens back to its original homeland. You can also bridge your erc20 assets from our token bridge from Ethereum Mainnet to xDAI Network and vice versa.</p>



<p>Currently, we are also using a decentralized protocol to broadcast our website to the world, by using IPFS for our hosting, it serves to protect us in the event our official .com domain being blocked, banned or taken down. Cryptocurrency has no apparent laws that govern its creation and usage in Trinidad and Tobago. As we attempt to disrupt the norms of traditional banking, trading and investments, our dapps are open source with documentation. Our smart contracts are immutable and will persist indefinitely. If desired, anyone can have a look at our repositories.</p>



<p>Join us and be a part of T&amp;T History in the cryptocurrency space.<br>For more information you can post your comments below, or Join our Discord, Telegram and social media pages. Crowdsale date to be finalized and announced soon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
